// Joel H. **Full Stack Developer**

elniu.dev / * based on Barcelona / o letjoel

About me

Creating websites and applications has been my passion since the early age of 15. I felt the need to better understand the world around me in a humanistic sense, so I studied for a Bachelor of Arts in Psychology and Humanities. Nevertheless, I quickly gravitated towards web development and have created multiple websites, ecommerce platforms, and web applications for over 10 years, particularly within the hospitality industry. This has allowed me to embark on an interesting professional journey that has given me a growth-oriented mindset and a deep understanding of transparent and honest communication. Always eager for knowledge, I have continued to update my technological skills through professional training to improve continuously. I enjoy my great hobby, which fortunately is also my profession.

Education

MERN Bootcamp

Barcelona, Spain

Cycle touring.

FACTORIA F5

Oct. 2022

Hiking.

Full stack developer (850h).

Mention in philosophy.

TBS video games.

University Degree in Humanities UPF (POMPEU FABRA UNIVERSITY)

Barcelona, Spain Jun. 2014

Languages

Interests

English C1 (British Council)

Spanish. Catalan C2.

Skills

- ✓ HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript
- √ React, Next js, Vue js, Tailwind, jQuery, SASS
- ✓ Node js, Nest js, Express, Socket.io, Swagger.
- √ MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MS SQL.
- ✓ GraphQL, REST API | Authorization | Documentation.
- √ TDD, Jest, Git, GitHub Actions, AGILE, Jira, Clean code.
- ✓ Docker, AWS (S3, EC2), DigitalOcean.

Expertise

JavaScript ***

TypeScript ☆☆☆☆

C# PHP

\$\$ **

Python

**

Java

Experience

ERP

Barcelona, Spain Sep. 2023 - Jan. 2024

FREELANCER FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Dashboard and WebApp for an American company with customer management, fleet of trucks with routes, services, employees, invoices, etc. React, Apollo GraphQL, Recoil, PostgreSQL with Sequalize, and TypeScript.

IA Product

Barcelona, Spain Aug. 2023 - Sep. 2023

FREELANCER FULL STACK DEVELOPER

App with execution of AI Prompts for automation of internal processes. Developed with Vue. Pinia, TypeScript, Redis and MongoDB.

Real Estate

Barcelona, Spain Jul. 2023 - Aug. 2023

FREELANCER FULL STACK DEVELOPER

American real estate website with CMS. Tech. used: Next js, React and Headless CMS (Hygraph) with GraphQL and TypeScript.

Library of Things

Barcelona, Spain Feb. 2023 - Apr. 2023

FREELANCER FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Complex object lending app project for a municipal council. Node js full stack app: React, API with Nest js (Express), TypeScript, MySQL.

Multiple projects

From 2009

Apps and sites, using JavaScript, PHP, WordPress, E-commerce, videogames...